TARA MCKEEVER

30 OVER RD, FEASTERVILLE PA. 19053

taramckeever@verizon.net 215-688-6977

"...exceptional in her ability to meet the needs of her students in such a way that their achievements far exceed their expectations..."

Sister Shaun Thomas

Principal

"...my reading level and confidence went up because of the structure of your class..."

Heather W

Former Student

"...a level of confidence and accomplishment that emerges from each of her students..."

Susan Berman

Reading Specialist

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

Highly skilled and dual certified educator with 8 years of experience, working with typical and special needs students. Dedicated to creating a learning environment where all levels of achievement can be met. Possesses outstanding communication skills with students, parents, and educators alike.

CERTIFICATIONS

ELEMENTARY K-6 SPECIAL EDUCATION N-12

EDUCATION

2000-2003 TEMPLE UNIVERSITY PHILADELPHIA, PA BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN EDUCATION GPA 3.30 CUM LAUDE

1998-2000 COMMUNITY COLLEGE OF PHILADELPHIA PHILA, PA GPA 3.03

EXPERIENCE

ST. DOMINIC SCHOOL PHILADELPHIA, PA 1/2006-6/2012 LEAD LEARNING SUPPORT TEACHER GRADES 6-8

Created and implemented IEP's for learning disabled students Coordinated meetings for parents and specialists Collected and analyzed data to meet goals in IEP's Used accommodations and modifications to support mainstreamed students

BARTOW COUNTY SD CARTERSVILLE, GA 9/2003-2005 INTERRELATED SPECIAL EDUCATION TEACHER

Worked closely with classroom teacher to create lesson plans Created and implemented IEP's Collected and analyzed data to support IEP goals Provided push- in support to mainstreamed classroom

EXTRACURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

Title 1 tutoring program summer school spirit day committee dance-a-thon committee

Find additional information on PAREAP